[
    {
      "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "What is the meaning of Pakistan?",
      "correct_answer": "Holy Land",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Desert",
        "Land of five rivers",
        "Save Land"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Animals",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who is the first Governor General of Pakistan?",
      "correct_answer": "Muhammad Ali Jinnah",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Liaquat Ali Khan",
        "Farhan",
        "Ayub Khan"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Books",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "What was the major event of 1971?",
      "correct_answer": "Bangladesh broke away from Pakista",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Tashkent Agreement", "Nuclear Bomb", "Explosion in Depth"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Comics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who%20is%20the%20creator%20of%20the%20comic%20series%20%22The%20Walking%20Dead%22%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Robert%20Kirkman",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Stan%20Lee",
        "Malcolm%20Wheeler-Nicholson",
        "Robert%20Crumb"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Board%20Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": " In which year did Pakistan win the Cricket World Cup?",
      "correct_answer": "1992",
      "incorrect_answers": ["1867", "1996", "2011"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%Pakistan%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Islamabad",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Rio%20de%20Janeiro", "Dar%20es%20Salaam", "Karachi"]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "When%20did%20Poland%20recieve%20its%20independence%20from%20England%3F%20",
      "correct_answer": "1962",
      "incorrect_answers": ["1792", "1961", "1967"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Animals",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Kangaroos%20keep%20food%20in%20their%20pouches%20next%20to%20their%20children.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "category": "General%20Knowledge",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "In%202013%20how%20much%20money%20was%20lost%20by%20Nigerian%20scams%3F",
      "correct_answer": "%2412.7%20Billion",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "%2495%20Million",
        "%24956%20Million",
        "%242.7%20Billion"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "How%20old%20was%20Lyndon%20B.%20Johnson%20when%20he%20assumed%20the%20role%20of%20President%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F",
      "correct_answer": "55",
      "incorrect_answers": ["30", "40", "84"]
    }
    
    
  ]
  